[MUSIC PLAYING]
BRUNO DENUIT: 大家好
BRUNO DENUIT: Hi.
我是Bruno
I'm Bruno.
我是EnPlug的首席软件架构师
I'm the Chief Software Architect at EnPlug.
我们是第一家做数字标牌的开放软件平台
We are the first open software platform for digital signage.
在这个视频里  我将要给你们展现
In this video, I would like to show you
你怎么才能使用EnPlug平台来开发一个应用
how you can use the EnPlug platform to develop an app
并且在世界上的任何一个物理设备上展现你的内容
and deploy your content to any physical device in the world.
所以当我们开始做EnPlug的时候
So when we started EnPlug, we decided
我们决定从Android平台开始着手  因为它是一个开放的平台
to go with the Android platform, because it's an open platform.
这是非常有名的  并且这让我们可以在非常便宜的设备
It's very popular, and it also let us run our software
上运行我们的软件
on inexpensive hardware.
我们决定使我们的软件成为一个开放的平台
We decided to make our software an open platform
所以那些想展示自己页面在
so that the people who want to bring
数字世界的人可以通过
their content into the digital world
我们的平台专注于自身价值增长
could focus on their value add by building
并创建他们的应用
an app on our platform, and wouldn't
并且他们并不需要担心我们所担心的所有细节问题
have to worry about all the details that we had to worry about.
所以你怎么才能开始做呢
So how do you start doing that?
你怎么才能开始在EnPlug的平台上写应用
How do you start writing an app for the EnPlug platform?
访问developers.enplug.com
Go to developers.enplug.com.
注册并且下载我们的SDK
Sign up and download our SDK.
我们的SDK由两个部分组成
Our SDK is made up of two parts.
明显的是  这里有为写我们实际运行在设备上
Obviously, there is the SDK for actually writing the app
的应用所准备的SDK
that we run on the devices.
这个将为Android所使用  但是它也同样
It will run for Android, but it also
可以运行在桌面端  Mac和Windows以及我所提及的Chrome OS
runs in desktop, Mac and Windows, and now Chrome OS, like I mentioned.
另外的部分就是如果你想让你的应用
And the other part is if you want your app
更好地可制定化  如果有一些配置
to be more customized, if there are certain configuration
是你想让你的用户进行选择的
settings that you want the user to select,
然后你可以使用我们的网页SDK来创建一个网页
then you can use our web SDK to create a web page,
并且让用户在EnPlug保存所有的配置以及各种事务
and have the user save all these configuration and things in EnPlug.
我们在Github上有两个样例应用
We have two examples on GitHub of sample apps
你们可以下载并且使用它们
that you can download and use out of the box.
第一个样例是一个非常简单的应用
The first one is a very simple app
能够允许你展现任何样式的网页
that allows you to show any kind of web page.
所以你能够从头开始做
So you can get going from the start.
只需要下载那个应用  让它指向你的网站
Just download that app, point it to your websites,
然后它将展现在屏幕上
and it will start showing on the screen.
第二个应用是为那些
The second app is for people who want
有点基础并且想创建他们自己的应用的人准备的
to go a little bit further and create their own app,
他们想定制他们自己的应用
customize their own app.
并且那个包含了一个在我们平台上创建应用的一个框架
And that contains a framework for creating an app on our platform.
这里有一个我们网页应用的一个样例
So here you have an example of our web app
你可以配置你自己的独特的应用
where you can configure your different apps.
你可以把他们打开或者关闭
You can toggle them on and off.
我选了Waitlist.me的应用来展示怎么来配置它
I selected Waitlist.me app to show how to configure it.
你可以去配置你的Waitlist应用
You can go and configure your Waitlist app.
它向你申请连接Waitlist.me的账户
It asks you to connect with an account on Waitlist.me.
所以这是一个EnPlug和第三方平台
So this is an example of the integration between EnPlug
集成的样例
and a third party.
输入你的Waitlist的证书
Type in your credentials for Waitlist.
你选择了你登陆的地点
You select the location that you are checked in with.
并且输入一些文本  一些标签
And type some text, some tagline.
最少的聚会人数
Minimum number of people.
这些是Waitlist.me的所有配置信息
These are all configuration settings for Waitlist.me.
你保存它  并且它展示
You save it, and it shows up preview of how
你的屏幕的样子的预览
your screen will look like.
我希望你们体验一下EnPlug
I hope you check out EnPlug.
去developers.enplug.com
Go to developers.enplug.com.
注册  下载我们的SDK  试用它  然后你就会发现
Sign up, download our SDK, try it out, and you'll see how easy
这是多么简单多么开心的事情
and how much fun you will have.
谢谢
Thank you.
[MUSIC PLAYING]